{
    "id": "81fe747e761f49babfb6b7c56a59dfae",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The escaped prisoner gave himself ................................... when he was cornered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He left a letter ....................................... when he spelt his name.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Never put ...................................... till tomorrow what you can do today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We must learn to put ........................................... the rising prices.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up with",
                "up",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He carried ............................................. the death wishes of his father.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The fog passed ...................................... when the sun rose.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We must provide ........................................ the education of our children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am counting ...................................... his help and support.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "One must learn to cope .................................. failure and disappointments.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They are looking ....................................... a bride for their son.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}